Joe Hollenbach

Software Engineer

linkedin.com/in/joe-hollenbach

github.com/justjoe19

joe-h.netlify.app

Summary

- Experience with Python, Django, HTML, Javascript, and React
- Experience with Mac and PC hardware repair and troubleshooting and repair
- Experience with networking
- Job history of management and leadership experience

Skills

HTML; CSS; Javascript; Python; Java;
Web Development; SQL; Node.js; Django;
MongoDB; MySQL; Version Control; GitHub;
Bash; Unix; Linux; Networking;
Responsive Web Design; Cloud Computing;
Hardware and Software Troubleshooting;
Virtualization; Computer Repair;
Technical Support; User Interface Design;
Front-End Development;
Object-Oriented Programming

Work Experience

December 2021 - present

Mishawaka, IN

Apple, Inc. - Expert

- Perform face-to-face technical support for iPhone, iPad, Apple Watch, and Mac
- Provide customers with issue troubleshooting, product diagnosis and potential solutions
- Leader in product sales, product knowledge, and customer satisfaction

January 2019 - June 2021

Mishawaka, IN

Jordan Auto Group - Acquisions Manager

- In charge of purchasing and pricing up to 250vehicle inventory
- Appraise customer trade-ins and accurately estimate reconditioning cost
- Oversee and support reconditioning process for each vehicle

Education

October 2020 - March 2024

South Bend, IN

Associate of Applied Science - Software Development

Ivy Tech Community College 3.9 GPA

Certifications

- Software Development Technical Certificate
 Ivy Tech Community College, December 2022
- Software Application Developer Certificate
 Ivy Tech Community College, May 2023
- AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner
 Amazon Web Services, May 2023
- A+ Certification

CompTIA, March 2024